Guide to the South Asian Pamphlets Collection, 1920-2005 (bulk 1950-2000) RL.01235
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- India Pamphlets, 1920-2005, bulk 1960-1990, 177 boxes
  - Communal Violence and Ethnic Conflict, 1948-1990, 2 boxes
    - Ramjanma Bhoomi - Honour People's Sentiments. Advani, L. K. New Delhi, India: 1989. (Box IN-21)
      Speech delivered by L.K. Advani Aug. 7, 1989, Rajya Sabha.
    - Ranchi Riots Inquiry Report X-Rayed. Noorani, A.G. New Delhi, Sampradayikta Virodhi Committee, India: 196-? (Box IN-21)
    - Recent Communal Riots: A Report. Bharatiya Jana Sangh. New Delhi, Bharatiya Jana Singh Publication, India: 1968. (Box IN-21)
    - Religious Riots ahead in India? Swamy, K. N. Vijyawada, Swamy Publications, India: 196-? (Box IN-21)
    - Report of the Commission of Inquiry into the Police Firing at Ramnagaram. Hiremath, D. P. Bangalore, [The Author]. India: 1981. (Box IN-21)
    - RSS - The Guilty. Communist Party of India. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1981. (Box IN-21)
      Jamshedpur Riot Inquiry Commission Findings.
    - RSS and Jana Sangh. Rao, C. Rajeswara. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1969. (Box IN-21)
    - Save Punjab Save India. Malhotra, Avtar Singh. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1984. (Box IN-21)
    - Secularism in Action: A Fraud, a Conspiracy to Destroy Hinduism. Joshi, P. N. New Delhi, Rashtriya Hindu Manch, India: 1990. (Box IN-21)
    - Shiv Sena and the Bombay Riots. Dange, S. A. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1969. (Box IN-21)
    - Three Eminent Personalities on the Ram Janambhoomi- Babri Masjid Controversy. Tripathi, Kamalapati, and Anand, Mulk Raj, and Mukherjee, Hiren. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1989. (Box IN-21)
    - UNP Organised Anti-Tamil Riots in Sri Lanka. Communist Party of India. New Delhi, Communist Party of India, India: 1983. (Box IN-21)
    - Why Communal G.O.? Ramasami, Periyar E. V. Madras, Periyar Self-Respect Propaganda Institution, India: 1983. (Box IN-21)
    - Why Rathayatra? Advani, L. K. Bangalore, Jagarana Prakashana Trust, India: 1990. (Box IN-21)
      An interview of the BJP president with Vinod Sharma of the Hindusthan Times.
  - Cooperative Movements,1962-1973, 2 boxes
    The 37 pamphlets in this section were published by official government agencies and cooperative groups, and discuss cooperative movements in agriculture, education, banking, and rural economic development in general.
    - Annual Administration Report on the Working of Co-operative Societies in Tripura as on 30th June, 1965. [Tripura], India: 1965. (Box IN-22)
    - Block Level Reports. New Delhi, Ministry of Community Development and Cooperation, India: 1965. (Box IN-177 (oversize))
    - Bombay Co-operative Societies Act 1925, The. The Press Workers' Printing & Publishing Society. Delhi, India: 1950. (Box IN-22)
      As Extended to the Province of Delhi.
    - Community Development through Sahakari Samaj. Dey, S. J., and India. Ministry of Community Development And Co-operation. New Delhi, India: 1962. (Box IN-22)
    - Community Development. Indian Cooperative Union. New Delhi, India: 1961. (Box IN-22)
      A Pilot Project under non-official auspices- shows how a Community Development Programme can be conducted as an effective instrument of productivity…
    - Comparative Study of Facts and Figures of Co-operative Movement in Rajasthan during 1966-69. Rajasthan. Jaipur, Co-operative Societies, India: 1970. (Box IN-22)
      Sahakari Vyvahar Pustakmala - 20.
    - Cooperation and Social Justice. Weeraman, P. E. New Delhi, International Cooperative Alliance, India: 1976. (Box IN-22)
      Cooperative Series, 20.
    - Co-operation: A Pictorial Presentation. India. Ministry Of Food, Agriculture, Community Development And Cooperation. New Delhi, Publications Division, India: 1966. (Box IN-22)
    - Co-operative Farming: Planning and Programming. India. Ministry of Community Development And Cooperation. New Delhi, India: 1965. (Box IN-22)
    - Co-operative Marketing and Processing. India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Delhi, Publictaions Division, India: 1961. (Box IN-22)
    - Co-Operative Movement in Meghalaya. Directorate of Information and Public Relations, Meghalay, Shillong. Shillong, Directorate of Information and Public Relations, Meghalay,India: 1982. (Box IN-22)
    - Co-operative Movement in Mysore State: Progress at a Glance. India. Department Of Co-operation. Bangalore, Mysore State Co-operative Union, India: 1969. (Box IN-22)
    - Co-operative Movement in Orissa: A Profile, 1968-69. Orissa. Co-operative Societies. Bhubaneswar, The Orissa Co-operative Union, India: 1969. (Box IN-22)
    - Co-operative Movement in Orissa: A Profile, 1969-70. Orissa. Co-operative Societies. Bhubaneswar, The Orissa Co-operative Union, India: 1970. (Box IN-22)
    - Co-operative Movement in Orissa: A Profile, 1971-72. Orissa. Co-operative Societies. Bhubaneswar, The Orissa Co-operative Union, India: 1972. (Box IN-22)
    - Co-operative Movement in Rajasthan at a Glance. Rajasthan. Jaipur, India: 1967. (Box IN-22)
      A Comparative Study Of Some Important Types Of Co-operative Societies During I, II and III Five Year Plans.
    - Co-operative Movement in Rajasthan: Important Statistics. Co-operative Department, Rajasthan, (Statistics Section). Jaipur, India: 197-? (Box IN-22)
    - Co-operative Processing. India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Delhi, India: 1962. (Box IN-22)
    - Cooperatives and Agricultural Implements. National Co-operative Development Corporation. New Delhi, India: 1967. (Box IN-22)
    - Cooperatives and Chemical Fertilisers. National Cooperative Development Corporation. New Delhi, India: 1966. (Box IN-22)
    - Co-operatives Make a Headway. Jammu and Kashmir. Jammu, Directorate of Information, India: 1965. (Box IN-22)
    - Educating the Young In Co-operation. India. Ministry of Community Development And Cooperation. New Delhi, Publications Division, India: 1966. (Box IN-22)
    - Evaluation Report on Fisheries Co-operative Societies, 1972. Directorate of Evaluation and Manpower. Bangalore, Government of Mysore, India: 1972. (Box IN-22)
    - Facts About Cooperation In India. India. Ministry Of Food, Agriculture, Community Development And Cooperation. New Delhi, India: 1970. (Box IN-22)
    - Facts About Cooperation In India. India. Ministry Of Food, Agriculture, Community Development And Cooperation. New Delhi, India: 1975. (Box IN-22)
    - Glimpses Of Cooperation In India. India. Directorate of Advertising And Visual Publicity. New Delhi, India: 1969. (Box IN-22)
    - Housing Co-operatives. Bihar. Co-operative Department. Patna, India: 1964. (Box IN-22)
      Co-operation Publication 7th.
    - How to Organise a Village Service Co-operative. India. Ministry Of Food, Agriculture, Community Development And Cooperation. New Delhi, India: 1968. (Box IN-22)
    - International Co-operation: The Way to Peace and Prosperity. Naik, V. P., and Maharashtra. Directorate of Publicity. Bombay, India: 1965. (Box IN-22)
    - Marketing of Cane through Cane Growers Co-operatives Societies. Bihar. Co-operative Department. Patna, India: 1964. (Box IN-23)
      Co-operation Publication 12th.
    - Model Blue-Prints of Cooperative Processing Units for Paddy, Oil Seeds, Cotton and Composite Units. National Cooperative Development And Warehousing Board. New Delhi, India: 1962. (Box IN-23)
    - Model Cooperative Societies Law, A. Weeraman, P. E. New Delhi, International Cooperative Alliance, India: 1971. (Box IN-23)
    - National Co-operative Development Corporation: Organization and Functions. National Cooperative Development Cooperation. New Delhi, India: 1964? (Box IN-23)
    - Report on Study of Viability of Primary Agricultural Credit Societies, a Bench Mark Survey (1968-69). Apte, S. G., and India. Planning Commission. New Delhi, India: 1973. (Box IN-23)
    - Returned USAID Participants - An Evaluation Study. India. Directorate of Evaluation And Manpower. [Mysore], India: 1968. (Box IN-23)
    - Selected Statistics on Co-operative Credit In India. Reserve Bank of India. Bombay, India: 1969. (Box IN-23)
    - Souvenir: State Level Co-operative Development Conference. Assam. Gauhati, India: 1984. (Box IN-23)
    - Success in Co-operation. India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. New Delhi, Publications Division, India: 1967. (Box IN-23)
    - Why Consumers' Cooperative Stores? India. Ministry of Community Development And Cooperation. New Delhi, Department Of Cooperation, India: 1966. (Box IN-23)
  - Dams, 1965-1990, 1 box
    Published by national and state official government agencies, these 22 pamphlets provide information on the environmental, political and economic impact of dams and various water harnessing projects.
    - Bridge across Son River on Rajegaon Kirnapur Lanji Road, Distt. Balaghat (M.P.). Madhya Pradesh Public Works Dept., Buildings and Roads Branch. Raipur, Public Works Dept., Buildings and Roads Branch, India: 1969. (Box IN-24)
    - Colossal Risk: Social, Ecological and Safety Aspects of Tehri Dam (and other Large Dam Projects in Himalayan Region), A. Dogra, Bharat. New Delhi, [The Author], India: 1990. (Box IN-24)
      Social Change Paper 16.
    - Damodar Valley Project. Damodar Valley Corporation, Information Dept., Calcutta. Calcutta, Information Dept., India: 1966. (Box IN-24)
      Prepared for the Sixth Congress of the Int'l Commission on Irrigation and Drainage, New Delhi, 4th January to 15th January, 1966.
    - DVC: An Introspection. Mookerjea, Debes. Calcutta, Damodar Valley Corporation, India: 197-? (Box IN-24)
    - 15 Years of DVC. Damodar Valley Corporation Information Dept., Calcutta. Calcutta, India: 196-? (Box IN-24)
    - Gandak Project: Work and Progress. Bihar. River Valley Projects Dept. Patna, India: 1966. (Box IN-24)
    - India's Temples of the Nehru Age. Misra, S. D. New Delhi, Ministry of Irrigation and Power, India: 1965. (Box IN-24)
      A Bhagraith Pamphlet.
    - Kosi Project, The. Bihar. River Valley Projects Dept. Patna, India: 1966. (Box IN-24)
    - Life Story of Lakha Majhi: Transformation of Life in D.V.C. Area. Damodar Valley Corporation. Calcutta, Damodar Valley Corporation Information Dept., India: 196-? (Box IN-24)
      Transformation of life in D.V.C. Area.
    - Loss of Head Due to Change in Direction and Due to Transitions and Bends Combined. Singh, Santokh, and Paul, T. C., and Sakhuja, V. S. and S. P. Bansal. New Delhi, Central Board of Irrigation and Power, India: 1984. (Box IN-24)
    - Nagarjunasagar: Inter-State Controversy. Rao, R. P. Narayanaguda, [The Author], India: 1967. (Box IN-24)
    - Narmada Valley Development: A View Point. Madhya Pradesh. Directorate of Information and Publicity. [n.p.], Directorate of Information and Publicity, India: 196-? (Box IN-24)
    - Narmada Valley Project and Madhya Pradesh. Directorate of Information & Publicity, Madhya Pradesh. Bhopal, Directorate of Information & Publicity, India: 1967. (Box IN-24)
    - Our River Valley Projects. India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Delhi, Publications Division, Ministry of I. and B., India: 1961. (Box IN-24)
    - Sone Barrage Project, The. India. Patna, Secretariat Press, India: 1965. (Box IN-24)
    - Stop the Construction of The Kharkhai Dam in the interest of Tribals & Nation. Tribal Documentation Centre, Bihar. Bihar, Tribal Documentation Centre, India: 1985? (Box IN-24)
    - Tehri Dam, The: A Prescription for Disaster. The Indian National Trust for Art and Cultural Heritage. New Delhi, INTACH, India: 1987. (Box IN-24)
      The INTACH Environmental Series, No. 6.
    - Tehri Dam Project - How Expert Opinion is Undermined. Dogra, Bharat. New Delhi, [The Author], India: 1990. (Box IN-24)
      Social Change Paper 16C.
    - Ten Questions on Tehri Dam Project. Dogra, Bharat. New Delhi, [The Author], India: 1990. (Box IN-24)
      Social Change Paper 16A.
    - Tungabhadra: The Life Line. Mysore. Director of Publicity and Information. Bangalore, India: 1966. (Box IN-24)
    - Water for Peace: A Note on the Water-Supply Conditions in the Deccan Trap Area. Apte, N. G. Poona, Maharashtra State, India: 19--? (Box IN-24)
      Submitted to the Int'l Conference by the Tilak Maharashtra Vidyapeetha.
    - World Bank's Poverty Increasing Projects Suvarnarekha and Narmada. Dogra, Bharat. New Delhi, [The Author], India: 1990? (Box IN-24)
      Social Change Paper 23.
  - Defense, 1963-1983, 1 box
    The 23 pamphlets in this section were published by official government agencies, political parties and individuals; they provide information on civil defense, armed forces, disarmament, popular literature on various aspects of India's preparedness against attacks by neighbors, and organization of Indian defenses.
    - Air Force Day. India. Ministry of Defence. New Delhi, India: 1968. (Box IN-25)
    - Camouflage. Natu, P. N., and Doraiswami, S. New Delhi, National Council of Educational Research and Training, India: 1963. (Box IN-25)
      Military Science Circle.
    - Chinese Aggression and Third Plan. Calcutta, Artha Vanijya Gabesana Mandir, India: 196-? (Box IN-25)
      Monograph No. 184.
    - Citizen's Guide for Civil Defence, A. Maharashtra. Director of Publicity. Bombay, India: 1966. (Box IN-25)
    - Defence. Subrahmanyam, K. New Delhi, Publications Divison, Govt. of India, India: 1972. (Box IN-25)
      25th Anniversary of India's Independence Series.
    - Disarmament. All India Congress Committee. New Delhi, AICC(I) Publication, India: 1983? (Box IN-25)
      Presents initiatives taken in India toward achieving disarmament.
    - Expected Betrayal, The. Patodia, D. N., and Patel, Dahyabhai V. Bombay, Swatantra Party Publication, India: 1968. (Box IN-25)
      Soviet Arms for Pakistan.
    - Fate of Macmahanline! Swamy, K. N. Vijyawada, Swamy Publications, India: 1959. (Box IN-25)
    - Harvest of Glory. India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Delhi, India: 1965. (Box IN-25)
    - India: Nuclear Challenge and Indian Response. India. Ministry of External Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1980. (Box IN-25)
    - Indian Navy, The. India. Ministry of Defence. New Delhi, India: 1963. (Box IN-25)
    - India's Defence Forces Since Independence. India. Ministry of Defence. New Delhi, India: 1966. (Box IN-25)
    - Know Your Air Force. Dhar, Chandrakala, and Bhatia, Shakuntala. New Delhi, National Council of Educational Research & Training, India: 1963. (Box IN-25)
      Schools and the National Emergency.
    - Know Your Navy. Sethi, Janak. New Delhi, National Council of Educational Research & Training, India: 1963. (Box IN-25)
    - Light Rescue. Sasta Sahitya Mandal, New Delhi. New Delhi, Sasta Sahitya Mandal Publication, India: 1962. (Box IN-25)
    - National Cadet Corps Act, The. India. Ministry of Law. Delhi, India: 1963. (Box IN-25)
      (As modified up to the 1st July, 1963).
    - Our Defences. India. Ministry of Information & Broadcasting. Delhi, India: 1966. (Box IN-25)
    - Pictorial Story of Civil Defence. India. Director General, Civil Defence, Ministry of Home Affairs. New Delhi, Ministry of Home Affairs, India: 1963. (Box IN-25)
    - Policeman Your Friend. Lal, Chaman. New Delhi, [The Author], India: 1971. (Box IN-25)
    - Story of Defence, The (1947-1972). India. Ministry of Defence. New Delhi, India: 1972. (Box IN-25)
    - What Every Citizen of Delhi Must Know. India. Ministry of Defence. New Delhi, India: 1963. (Box IN-25)
      Some Facts about: Civil Defence, Home Guards, Rifle Training.
    - You and Civil Defence. India. Ministry of Home Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1963. (Box IN-25)
      What is Civil Defence?/ Why you need Civil Defence?/ What you can do now in Civil Defence?.
    - Your Role in the National Emergency. India. Ministry of Information & Broadcasting. New Delhi, India: 1963. (Box IN-25)
      A Guide book for the Citizens of Delhi.
  - Disasters, 1965-1989, 1 box
    These eight pamphlets were published by official government agencies and NGOs and relate to natural and industrial disasters.
    - Assam Floods - '88. Assam. Janasanyog. [Guwahati, Govt. of Assam], India: 1988. (Box IN-26)
      Some view points.
    - Bhopal Disaster Aftermath: An Epidemiological and Socio-medical Survey, The. Medico Friend Circle. Bangalore, India: 1985. (Box IN-26)
    - Day of Disaster, The. Maharashtra. Director of Publicity. Bombay, India: 1968. (Box IN-26)
      Story of Koyna Quake.
    - Disaster Management in Assam. Das, H. N., Govt. of Assam. Guwahati, Assam Govt., India: 1989. (Box IN-26)
    - In the Refugee Camp. Vora, Raghuvir. Ahmedabad, Gujarat State Bangla-Desh Relief Committee, India: 197-? (Box IN-26)
    - Relief & Rehabilitation: Bird's Eye View. Jammu. Directorate of Information. Jammu, India: 1965. (Box IN-26)
    - Settlement or Sell-Out: Bhopal. Delhi Science Forum. New Delhi, India: 1989. (Box IN-26)
      On Bhopal industrial tragedy.
    - Voices from Bhopal. Bhopal Group for Information and Action, Bhopal. Bhopal, [The Author], India: 198-? (Box IN-26)
      Based on recorded interviews with Bhopal gas victims.
  - Economics, 1957-1990s, 15 boxes
    The 379 pamphlets in the Economics series cover a wide range of issues and are arranged in two divisions: Economic Development and Economic Policy. The publications in Economic Policy are further subdivided into three groupings: general issues (the largest section by far, with 261 pamphlets); central government planning; and regional economic policies and efforts. Further descriptions follow below.
    - Economic Development, 1965-1983, 2 boxes
      The 38 pamphlets were published by official government agencies and political parties between 1965 and 1983, and provide information on general economic development, economic development at the regional, federal and local levels including specific areas, cities and metropolitan areas.
      - Assam Is Back on the Rails. Gauhati Artists' Guild. Assam, Janasanyog, India: 1983. (Box IN-27)
      - Assam on 15th August, 1965. Assam. Directorate of Information and Public Relations. Gauhati, India: 197-? (Box IN-27)
      - Assam: General Guidelines For the Preparation of Sub-Divisional Plans. Assam. Directorate of Information and Public Relations. Shillong, India: 1979. (Box IN-27)
      - Calcutta Metropolitan District. West Bengal Industrial Development Corporation Limited. Calcutta, India: 1965. (Box IN-27)
        Statement Showing Number of Municipalities, Non-Municipalities, Urban Units And Mouzas Falling Within The Calcutta Metropolitan District Boundary.
      - Changing Face of Goa, Daman & Diu. Goa, Daman and Diu. Dept. of Information and Tourism. Panjim, India: 1965. (Box IN-27)
        A Brief Survey.
      - Co-operation for National Progress. Gandhi, Indira. India. Ministry of I. and B. New Delhi, India: 1981. (Box IN-27)
        Speech of the prime minister in Rajya Sabha, 25th Feb. 1981.
      - Dandakaranya: From an Unsettled Past to a Secure Future. India. Ministry of Rehabilitation. Delhi, India: 1960. (Box IN-27)
      - Decade of Progress (1953 to 1963), A. Jammu and Kashmir. Dept. of Information. Srinagar, Jammu and Kashmir Govt., India: 1963? (Box IN-27)
      - Delhi in the New Perspective. Engineering Dept. New Delhi, India: 1971. (Box IN-27)
      - Delhi on the Move. India. Director of Information & Publicity. Delhi, India: 1971. (Box IN-27)
      - Delhi: Facts at a Glance. Delhi Administration. Delhi, Director of Information & Publicity, India: 1970. (Box IN-27)
      - Emergency and the 20-Point Economic Programme as " Organization Change" Strategies in Public Sector. Pillai, K. J. New Delhi, India: 1975? (Box IN-27)
        Attaining Peak Performance Through Changed Industrial Relations Climates.
      - Eye for Calcutta, An. Basu, Samar. Calcutta, India: 1982? (Box IN-27)
      - Fact Sheets on Rajasthan. Rajasthan. Directorate of Public Relations. Jaipur, India: 1966? (Box IN-27)
      - Four Years of Progress: Delhi Administration. Delhi Administration. New Delhi, Director of Information and Publicity, India: 1971. (Box IN-27)
      - Functions and Organisation - Planning Research and Action Institute. Planning Research and Action Institute, Uttar Pradesh. Lucknow, [The Author], India: 1970. (Box IN-27)
        P.R.A.I. Publication No. 377.
      - Gulbarga on March. City Municipal Council, Gulbarga. Gulbarga, India: 1970? (Box IN-27)
        Souvenir.
      - Himachal Pradesh: 23 Years Of Progress. Himachal Pradesh. Director of Public Relations. Simla, India: 1970? (Box IN-27)
      - India Today: Basic Facts. India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. New Delhi, India: 1967? (Box IN-27)
      - India Today: Basic Facts. India. Directorate of Advertising and Visual Publicity. New Delhi, Ministry of I. and B., India: 1981. (Box IN-27)
      - India: Dynamic Progress Through Democracy. Embassy of India. Washington, D.C., USA: 198-? (Box IN-27)
      - Jammu & Kashmir - A Review of Progress. Jammu and Kashmir. Dept. of Information. Jammu, India: 1961. (Box IN-28)
      - Level of Economic Development in Punjab, 1971-72. Punjab. Economic And Statistical Organisation. Chandigarh, Economic Advisor To Government Punjab, India: 1972. (Box IN-28)
        Publication No. 173.
      - Meghalaya on the March. Meghalaya. Directorate of Information and Public Relations. Calcutta, India: 1974. (Box IN-28)
        Second Anniversary Meghalaya Statehood, January 21, 1974.
      - Meghalaya: Five Years of Progress. Meghalaya. Directorate of Information and Public Relations. Shillong, India: 1975. (Box IN-28)
      - Meghalaya: Some Facts and Figures. Barthakur, Pulin Behari, and Meghalaya. Directorate of Information & Public Relations. Shillong, India: 1973. (Box IN-28)
      - Meghalaya: Six Months of Achievements (February - August, 1988). Meghalaya. Directorate of Information and Public Relations. Shillong, India: 1988. (Box IN-28)
      - Meghalaya's March To Progress. Meghalaya. Directorate of Information and Public Relations. Shillong, India: 1974. (Box IN-28)
      - Mysore - A Profile in Commitment. Mysore. Dept. of Information and Tourism. Mysore, India: 1973. (Box IN-28)
      - Parivartan: Story of a Resurgent Village. India. Ministry of Industrial Development. New Delhi, Publications Division, India: 1965. (Box IN-28)
      - Pondicherry: 1954-72, A Profile of Progress. Pondicherry. Director of Tourism. Pondicherry, India: 1972. (Box IN-28)
      - Punjab: Inauguration Punjab. Director, Public Relations. Chandigarh, India: 1966. (Box IN-28)
        Souvenir, Nov 1, 1966.
      - Rajasthan: Strides in Progress. Rajasthan. Directorate of Public Relations. Jaipur, India: 1981. (Box IN-28)
      - Strategy for Development of Hill Areas. Parmar, Y. S. Simla, Govt. of Himachal Pradesh, India: 1973. (Box IN-28)
      - Towards a Fuller Life for Everybody. Gandhi, Indira. New Delhi, All India Congress Committee, India: 1972. (Box IN-28)
        Inaugural and concluding speeches at the Congress Leaders' Conference on 13th & 14th May, 1972.
      - Towards a New Trend of Approach to Development. Bara, Dominic and Boniface Minz. Bihar, Vikas Maitri, India: 1976. (Box IN-28)
      - Towards Self Reliance: Changing India. India. Ministry of Information and Broadcasting. Madras, Directorate of Advertising and Visual Publicity, India: 1972. (Box IN-28)
      - Working Group for Recommending the Fiscal and Financial Incentives for Starting Industries in Backward Areas. Ministry of Industrial Development, Internal Trade & Company Affairs. New Delhi, India: 1969. (Box IN-28)
        April 1969.
    - Economic Policy, 1957-1990s, 13 boxes
      - Central Government Five Year Plans, 1960s-1990s, 2 boxes